<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
	<learnBycastingSpells>If using abilities give proficiency experiance.</learnBycastingSpells>
	<CastProRequirement>If abilities have a proficiency requirement to cast.</CastProRequirement>
	<strictMightCastReuRequirement>If might skills requires knowing proficiencies instead of being able to learn proficiencies.</strictMightCastReuRequirement>
	<strictMagicCastReuRequirement>If magic spells requires knowing proficiencies instead of being able to learn proficiencies.</strictMagicCastReuRequirement>
	<CostScale>If ability costs scaled based on known proficiencies.</CostScale>
	<RelatedSpells>Related Spells</RelatedSpells>
	<MissingPro>Missing proficiencies:</MissingPro>
	<ProStatOffset>Proficiency Modifiers</ProStatOffset>
	<FailChance>Self teach fail chance.</FailChance>
	<FailChanceReport>The chane for an individual to fail to discover a class or spell when using this.</FailChanceReport>
	<ProficienciesMasterOffseter>If proficiencies enhanced stat modifier behaviour is enabled.</ProficienciesMasterOffseter>
	<UnlearnProOnClassGain>If a pawn will unlearn proficiencies that they normally would not use when gaining a class.</UnlearnProOnClassGain>
	<LLARoM_LearnMagicMissingProficiencies>{0} is not able to understand that tome.</LLARoM_LearnMagicMissingProficiencies>
	<LLARoM_LearnMightMissingProficiencies>{0} is not able to understand that manual.</LLARoM_LearnMightMissingProficiencies>
	<LLARoM_LearnSpellMissingProficiencies>{0} is not able to understand that scroll.</LLARoM_LearnSpellMissingProficiencies>
	<LLAROM_GemOfInsight>{USER_labelShort} used a gem of insight to learn {1}.</LLAROM_GemOfInsight>
	<StrictMightClassLearning>If a might class requires knowing proficiencies instead of being able to learn proficiencies.</StrictMightClassLearning>
	<StrictMagicClassLearning>If a magic class requires knowing proficiencies instead of being able to learn proficiencies.</StrictMagicClassLearning>
	<StrictSkillLearning>If a fighter skill requires knowing proficiencies instead of being able to learn proficiencies.</StrictSkillLearning>
	<StrictSpellLearning>If a magic spell requires knowing proficiencies instead of being able to learn proficiencies.</StrictSpellLearning>
	<ObscureCertianProficiencies>If magic and magic proficiencies are hidden if a pawn cannot learn them.</ObscureCertianProficiencies>
	<ObscureAllProficiencies>If all proficiencies are hidden if a pawn cannot learn them.</ObscureAllProficiencies>
	<LLRoM>Life Lessons and A Rimworld of Magic Intergration</LLRoM>
	<ClassRequiresProficiencies>If classes have learning requirements</ClassRequiresProficiencies>
	<AbilityRequiresProficiencies>If abilities have learning requirements</AbilityRequiresProficiencies>
	<XPMultiplier>Experiance from ability use multiplier.</XPMultiplier>
	<ValueXPMultiplier>{0}% of normal learn rate.</ValueXPMultiplier>
	<CanFailLearn>If there is a chance to fail an attempt to learn a class or an ability when self teaching, fail chace is determined by the object used.</CanFailLearn>
	<LLRoM_AutoLearnedClass>{0} made a breakthrough becoming {2} {1}.</LLRoM_AutoLearnedClass>
	<LLRoM_AutoLearnClassFail>{0} failed to make a breakthrough, cause: random chance.</LLRoM_AutoLearnClassFail>
	<LLRoM_FailAutoLearnedClassNoClasses>{0} failed to make a breakthrough, cause: no possible breakthroughs.</LLRoM_FailAutoLearnedClassNoClasses>
	<LLRoM_FailAutoLearnedClassUnknownError>{0} failed to make a breakthrough, cause: unknown.</LLRoM_FailAutoLearnedClassUnknownError>
	<CanSelfTeachClasses>If a pawn can learn attempt to learn a class at certain spots.</CanSelfTeachClasses>
	<CanOnlySelfTeachClasses>If classes can only be learned by interacting at certian spots.</CanOnlySelfTeachClasses>
	<CanSelfTeachSpells>If a pawn can attempt to learn a spell using a blank scroll.</CanSelfTeachSpells>
	<CanOnlySelfSpells>If spells can only be learned by using a blank scroll.</CanOnlySelfSpells>
	<CanSelfTeachSkills>If a pawn can attempt to learn a skill using a blank scroll.</CanSelfTeachSkills>
	<CanOnlySelfSkills>If skills can only be learned by using a blank scroll.</CanOnlySelfSkills>
	<LLRoMMustNotBeUndead>Must not be undead</LLRoMMustNotBeUndead>
	<LLRoMDisableInOptions>Disabled in options</LLRoMDisableInOptions>
	<LLRoMNotMagical>Must be magical</LLRoMNotMagical>
	<LLROMNoFailedtoLearnSpell>{0} failed to teach themself a spell.</LLROMNoFailedtoLearnSpell>
	<LLROMNoPossibleSpell>{0} already knows all the spells that they can learn.</LLROMNoPossibleSpell>
	<LLRoMNotMighty>Must be mighty</LLRoMNotMighty>
	<LLROMNoFailedtoLearnSkill>{0} failed to teach themself a skill.</LLROMNoFailedtoLearnSkill>
	<LLROMNoPossibleSkill>{0} already knows all the skills that they can learn.</LLROMNoPossibleSkill>
	<StatOffseterLable>Advance stat offset behaviours.</StatOffseterLable>
	<StatOffseterLableDesc>These will apply once mastered, and will increase the base value by the listed offsets.</StatOffseterLableDesc>
	<StatModiferLable>Advance stat modifier behaviours.</StatModiferLable>
	<StatModiferLableDesc>These will apply once master, and will multiply by the listed percents.</StatModiferLableDesc>
	<ClassProLockout>If gaining a class will block learning proficiencies not normally useable by the class (detection based on Hediffs).</ClassProLockout>
</LanguageData>